[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果我们看练习十，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If we look at exercise ten,
简单地说，我在练习10中想说的就是，
simply all that I'm saying with exercise ten is,
我给了你其中一个实现的代码实际上是。
I gave you the code from one of the implementations is actually the.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我给了你来自的代码，哪个实现？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I gave you the code from the, which implementation?
异步的味道来自回购的实现。
The asynquence flavored implementation from the repo.
所以我已经给了你那个代码，
So I've given you that code already,
它是在这个回购中建立的，它要求你首先做的是，
it's set up in this repo and what this is asking you to do is first,
研究这五种实现之间的异同。
to study the similarities and differences between these five implementations.
你不应该花那么多时间打开，因为你只有两个文件
Shouldn't take you that much time to open up because there's only two files that you
应该关心ui.js和Feeds.js，这两个实现中的每一个。
should care about the ui.js and the feeds.js, each of those implementations.
所以打开这两个ui.js，然后
So open up ui.js in those two, and
并排看，看看其中的一些不同之处。
look side by side look at some of the differences.
只是没有深入研究这些差异，但是
Study those differences just not deeply, but
只是为了大致了解事情的进展情况。
just to get a rough sense of how things are going.
然后查看UI和
And then look at the ui and
在练习10文件夹中的此资料库中提供的提要js。
feeds js that's presented in this repo that is in the exercise 10 folder.
这是异步风味的。
Which is the asynchronous flavored one.
现在你的任务是练习，如果你选择解决它。
Now your task for the exercise, should you choose to tackle it.
选择反应序列或
Pick either one of reactive sequences or
CSP，从我们刚才讨论的内容中，你更喜欢哪一个。
CSP, whichever one you like more from what we just talked about.
我不在乎。
I don't care.
选择这两种中的任何一种，试着把我已经有的顺序式风味的那一种
Pick either one of those two and try to turn the asequence flavored one that I've
为你提供了这种抽象。
provided you into that abstraction.
所以试着把它变成可观察到的反应序列一或
So try to take it and make it into the observable reactive sequences one or
尝试使它成为CSP之一，无论你喜欢哪一个。
try to make it into the CSP one, whichever one you'd like.
这是极具挑战性的。
This is super challenging.
我会告诉你这些实现中的每一个，
I'll tell you that each of those implementations,
当我第一次写的时候，花了我一天又一天的时间。
when I wrote them the first time, took me days and days.
所以我并不指望你能做到一个完整的事情，但是
So I'm not expecting you to get all the way there to a full complete thing, but
你也可以作弊，因为我给你提供了回购的固定版本，所以
you also can cheat cuz I've provided you the fixed versions on the repo, so
如果你需要一些提示。
if you need some hints.
但真正的重点是在接下来的几分钟里，
But really the point here is to just spend the next few minutes,
我们可能会休息15分钟左右。
we'll probably break for 15 minutes or so.
在接下来的15分钟里，试着研究这些差异，
Take the next 15 minutes and try to study these differences,
试着用你的手对它做一些改变，这会更具反应性。
try your hand at making some changes to it that would be more reactive.
感受一下做我们一直在练习的事情是什么感觉
And get a sense of what it's like to do what we've practiced all along in
本研讨会，但在一个更复杂的应用程序的上下文中这样做
this workshop, but doing so in the context of a much more sophisticated app
而不是我们简单的小承诺演示。
than our simple little promises demo.